http://www.jobdiagnosis.com/privacy-policy.php#timeline

Privacy Policy Information for JobDiagnosis.
Effective Date: February 19, 2016
PRIVACY POLICY
GENERAL
"This Privacy Statement applies to JobDiagnosis owned and operated by VHMnetwork, LLC. This Privacy Statement describes how JobDiagnosis collects and uses the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information."
Job Diagnosis ("JobDiagnosis") , we are committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the Job Diagnosis website, and the Job Diagnosis service, including software applications made available by VHMnetwork, LLC, such as the Job Diagnosis mobile device application, (together, the "Service"), and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy.
This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Service and not to any websites or services of third parties ("Third-Party Websites"), which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below.
BY USING THE SERVICE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY CEASE USING OR ACCESSING THE SERVICE.
Each time You access the Service, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Each time You use the Service, we recommend that you check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Service. For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy, below.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Statement, you should first contact us at admin@VHMnetwork.com
BY REGISTERING WITH OR USING THE WEBSITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
As used in this Privacy Policy, "Non-Personally-Identifying Information" is information that, without the aid
of additional information, cannot be directly associated with a specific person. "Personally-Identifying Information," by contrast, is information
such as a name or email address that, without more, can be directly associated with a specific person.
1. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
Job Diagnosis does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Job Diagnosis obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, Job Diagnosis will immediately delete such information from its database. Because Job Diagnosis does not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, Job Diagnosis has no such information to use or disclose to third parties. Job Diagnosis has designed this Privacy Policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").
2. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES
(a) Traffic Data.- Non-Personally Identifiable Information: Like most website operators, Job Diagnosis automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing the Service; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Service (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify You.Job Diagnosis analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help Job Diagnosis better understand who is using the Service and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Job Diagnosis is able to better design the Service to improve Your experience, and to serve You more relevant and interesting content and advertisements. From time to time, Job Diagnosis may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Service. Job Diagnosis does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personally Identifiable Information.
(b) Tracking technologies:Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by VHMnetwork LLC and our partners [marketing partners], affiliates, or analytics or service providers
[online customer support provider, etc]. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.
We use cookies for [our shopping cart, to remember users' settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication]. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited
(c) Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information.We use Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences.
Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here:
www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.
If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads.
You will continue to receive generic ads.
We may use third-party advertising companies to collect data and/or serve ads when you visit our website or application. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites or applications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Please keep in mind that your browser settings may not permit you to control the technologies utilized by these third-party companies.
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit parrable.com and search for information concerning the NAI opt-out tool.
(d) Personally Identifiable Information.
In order for You to use certain features of the Service, You will be asked to provide Job Diagnosis certain Personally Identifiable Information.
The Personally Identifiable Information that Job Diagnosis collects includes: (1) "Contact Data" (such as Your name, telephone phone number, mailing address and e-mail address); (2) "Demographic Data" (such as Your gender and zip code); and (3) "Third-Party Social Media Account Data" (such as Your account information for third-party social media accounts when you access the Services in connection to those accounts). In each case, You will be asked to provide Personally Identifiable Information; the Service will not gather it surreptitiously. JobDiagnosis does not request or collect sensitive financial or sensitive information such as Your credit card number, bank account information, or social security number in order to register with our Website. Job Diagnosis may supplement the Personally Identifiable Information You provide with additional Personally Identifiable Information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide such information to Job Diagnosis. You are under no obligation to provide Personally Identifiable Information, with the caveat that Your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the Service.
(e) Information You Make Public.
The Service
may contain features (e.g.instant messages, electronic messaging, etc.) that permit You to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, information or other, including Your Personally Identifiable Information.
Any information that You choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information over which Job Diagnosis is unable to exercise control.
You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose Your Personally Identifiable Information by means of such features, and You agree to assume all responsibility for doing so.
The purpose of Criteo Email is to find visitors of Criteo advertising clients' properties (websites, apps and newsletters) and send them personalized emails. Criteo uses cookies to single out users and then personalize ads based on their browsing experience. To learn more or opt out of Criteo Email click here (link to privacy.criteoemail.com/us/privacy-policy.html)
You may, instead of logging in through Facebook Connect or Twitter, create login credentials using your name and e-mail address.
3. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES
Job Diagnosis may also share it with third parties and our affiliate companies to develop and deliver targeted advertising through our Service and on websites of third parties. Job Diagnosis may combine Non-Personal Information collected through the Service
with additional Non-Personal Information collected from other sources. Job Diagnosis also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, Job Diagnosis may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to the Service and the most popular features or services accessed. This information does not contain any Personally-Identifying Information and may be used to develop website content and services that Job Diagnosis hopes you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.
Personally Identifiable Information.
(i) Generally.
Job Diagnosis uses Your Contact Data to send You information about Job Diagnosis and Job Diagnosis's products and services, and to contact You when necessary in connection with the Service. Job Diagnosis uses Your Financial Data to verify Your qualifications for certain features of the Service and, when necessary, to bill You. Job Diagnosis uses Your Demographic Data to customize and tailor Your experience on the Service.
Job Diagnosis uses Your Third-Party Social Media Account Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Policy of Facebook and the Privacy Policy of Twitter.
As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time Job Diagnosis may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Service.
(ii) Disclosure Practices.
Except under the following circumstances, Job Diagnosis will keep Your Personally Identifiable Information private, and will not share it with third parties.
Disclosure to Advertisers During Registration.
During the registration process you will be directed through a number of third party websites displaying advertisements for that may be of interest to you. If you select "Yes" on any of these advertisements or choose to complete the forms provided, you will be asked to submit Personally Identifying Information. In all cases, when you click on the submit button, Job Diagnosis will securely transfer your Personally Identifying Information to the third-party advertiser you selected. Job Diagnosis will not use the Personally Identifying Information that you submit for transfer to a third-party advertiser for our own purposes; nor will Job Diagnosis retain or disclose it. You may be prompted by some advertisers to answer additional questions. These pages may be "co-branded" or "framed." This means that they may appear to be part of the Service because they have a JobDiagnosis.com look and feel, but they are, in fact, part of the advertiser's website.
Some of the framed pages contain the following disclaimer at the bottom of the page: " *By submitting the form above I agree to provide this information to the advertiser and to be contacted by this advertiser directly."
Some other pages contain disclaimers that are substantially identical, but use varying phrasing to the same effect.
On these framed pages, Job Diagnosis does not collect any of the additional information You submit; the advertiser does, and it does not share this information with Job Diagnosis. The advertiser uses your information to deliver additional information to you about its particular product or service and perhaps for other purposes. Its collection and use of your information is subject to its own privacy policy.
Disclosure to Marketing Partners.
Job Diagnosis may utilize any and all Personally Identifiable Information to help our clients better understand the demographics of our target audiences as well as to support our marketing data products and services.
Job Diagnosis may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information to partner firms which may include third party marketing companies, affiliates, advertising agencies, and data aggregation companies.
When You elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.
Disclosure to Direct Mail Partners.
Job Diagnosis may also provide its postal mailing list to direct mail partners.
Disclosure in Connection with Service.
Job Diagnosis discloses Personally Identifiable Information to those who help it provide services, including without limitation those who perform technical, administrative, and data processing tasks such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security.
These services may include fulfilling orders, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through the Service.These companies are authorized to use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
Social Media.
Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These Features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.
License to User Content.
As stated in the Terms of Use, by using the Service, You grant the Job Diagnosis Parties the right to publish Your name and any username of Yours in connection with the Job Diagnosis Parties exercise of their license in and to Your User Content. You further waive any claims arising from the Job Diagnosis Parties exercise of that right. For additional information, see Terms of Use Section 16, regarding User Content.
By Law or to Protect Rights.
Job Diagnosis discloses Personally Identifiable Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or similar legal process or when Job Diagnosis believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Job Diagnosis, third parties or the public at large.
Business Transfers; Bankruptcy.
Job Diagnosis reserves the right to transfer all Personally Identifiable Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Job Diagnosis?s assets.
Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personally Identifiable Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if You are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it.
Personally Identifiable Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by Job Diagnosis?s successor organization.
Unpaid Accounts.
If You fail to pay any balance owed in consideration of services, Job Diagnosis may, as permitted by law, report Your Personally Identifiable Information, including without limitation Your unpaid balance, to consumer credit reporting services, collection agencies and others.
4. CONSENT TO RECEIVE ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS FROM JOB DIAGNOSIS
Without limitation, by registering for the Service and/or by providing your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number through the Service, you hereby expressly consent to receive electronic and other communications from Job Diagnosis, over the short term and periodically, including email and short-message service (?SMS? or ?text message?) communications, regarding the Service, new product offers, promotions, and other matters.
You may opt-out of receiving electronic communications at any time by (a) following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each communication; (b) editing your account details and preferences; (c) sending an email with ?UNSUBSCRIBE? in the subject line to This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it
in response to which message, and notwithstanding its content, Job Diagnosis reserves the right to send you notices about your account; or (d) to completely opt-out of any contact whatsoever, deactivating your account by sending a detailed email to This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it
or logging in and clicking the ?Cancel Account? button on the "My Info" Tab.
5. CONSENT TO RECEIVE ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS FROM OTHER JOB DIAGNOSIS USERS
Without limitation, by registering for the Service and/or by providing your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number through the Service, you hereby consent to receive electronic communications, including email, voice telephone call, and short-message service ("SMS") messages, instant messages, video conferencing, and other personal messages from other users of the Service.
To completely opt-out of any contact whatsoever from Job Diagnosis users, you may deactivate your account by sending a detailed email to
This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it
or logging in and clicking the "Cancel Account" button on the "My Info" Tab.
6. CONSENT TO RECEIVE ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS FROM JOB DIAGNOSIS PARTNER MARKETERS
Without limitation, by registering for the Service and/or by providing your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number through the Service, you hereby consent to receive, and openly and knowingly solicit, electronic communications, including email, voice telephone call, and SMS communications, from Job Diagnosis partner firms which may include third party marketing companies, affiliates, advertising agencies, and data aggregation companies regarding their services, including offers, promotions, and other related matters. You may opt-out of receiving electronic communications at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each communication.
Users will be responsible for directly contacting such third parties to request cessation of further marketing contacts.
7. SECURITY OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
Job Diagnosis takes security seriously. We utilize commercially reasonable safeguards to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personally Identifiable Information.. However, due to the realities of data security, Job Diagnosis is unable to guarantee that any information provided to us will not be accessed, hacked, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized parties.
8. LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION
You must promptly notify us if Your credit, bank, other financial institution information, user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such and event, we will remove that credit card number, bank account information, other financial institution information, user name or password from Your account and updated our records accordingly.
9. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, CORRECT and DELETE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
Job Diagnosis wants Your Personally Identifiable Information to be complete and accurate. As stated in the Terms of Use, by using the Service, You represent and warrant that all information You provide in connection with Your use of the Service is current, complete, and accurate, and that You will update that information as necessary to maintain its completeness and accuracy. To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to or delete Your Personally Identifiable Information, visit Your personal account.We will respond to your request to access within a reasonable timeframe.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.
We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
10. INFORMATION HOSTED IN THE UNITED STATES
The Service is hosted in the United States of America and is subject to U.S. state and federal law. If you are accessing the Service from other jurisdictions, please be advised that you are transferring your Personally Identifiable Information to Job Diagnosis in the United States, and by using the Service, you consent to that transfer and to abide by the applicable laws of applicable states and U.S. federal law concerning your use of the Service and your agreements with us. Any persons accessing the Service from any jurisdiction with laws or regulations governing the use of the Internet, including personal data collection, use and disclosure, that create rights or obligations materially different from those of the U.S. jurisdictions mentioned herein may only use the Service in a manner lawful in their jurisdiction. If Your use of the Service would be unlawful in Your jurisdiction, including by creating obligations that differ materially from this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Service.
11. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES,BLOGS
Job Diagnosis neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites. Accordingly, Third-Party Websites are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personally Identifiable Information provided directly to them by Job Diagnosis. Before visiting or providing Personally Identifiable Information to a Third-Party Website, You should inform Yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in Your discretion, protect Your privacy.
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog or community forum, contact us at admin@VHMnetwork.com.
In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why
12. PROMOTIONAL ACTIVITIES
From time to time, Job Diagnosis may conduct contests, giveaways and other promotions (collectively, ?Promotional Activities?). Any information submitted in connection with Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. From time to time, Job Diagnosis may also ask You to participate in surveys designed to help Job Diagnosis improve the Service. Any Personally Identifiable Information provided to Job Diagnosis in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form.
13. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Job Diagnosis reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such update, change or modification on this page. Any such addition, update, change or modification will be effective immediately upon posting.
Unless Job Diagnosis obtains Your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy.If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective.
14. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to our privacy officer as listed below.
Last Updated January 2020
Your right to opt out of sale of your personal information
Under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA), beginning January 1, 2020, California residents have the right to opt out of the sale of personal information about them or their household, such as (though not limited to) their name, postal or email address, and other personally identifying information. You need not be physically present in California to exercise this right provided that you have a current California residence.
This right is subject to certain exemptions. For example, the law does not apply to information that has been aggregated and/or de-identified such that it could not reasonably be used to identify you. It also does not apply to information that we share with third-party service providers in order for them to perform certain business functions for us.
How to exercise your opt-out rights or other California privacy rights
If you would like to exercise any of your rights provided by the CCPA, such as the right to access or delete your personal information, or to opt out of the sale or future sale of your personal information you or your authorized agent or representative may contact us via the following methods:
Email: rmartin@vhmnetwork.com
Phone: 646-723-4374
Postal Mail: VHMnetwork LLC, 270 Greenwich Ave.,Greenwich, CT 06830
Or by webform link provided here: Do not sell my personal information.
There is no charge for making privacy-related requests.
In some cases, we may be unable to fulfill your request because we have no way to verify your identity to the standard the law and/or its associated regulations require. For example (but without limitation), if you have visited our website, but never registered as a user, or applied for a job, or interacted with us via email or other means, we probably do not have enough information to confirm your identity to even a "reasonable degree of certainty" (as the applicable regulations may define that term). Also, in addition to any other exemptions applicable law and/or regulation may provide to your rights under the CCPA (particularly with regard to the deletion of your personal information), we may be unable to delete certain information (e.g., our web host's server and error logs) for technical reasons.
As with the right to opt out, the other rights provided by the CCPA are subject to certain exemptions and exceptions, as specified in the applicable federal statutes and/or associated regulations issued by California's Office of the Attorney General. Those statues and/or regulations may also stipulate the maximum time allowed for acknowledging and responding to a request. There is no charge for making privacy-related requests.
Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information.
You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must:
•
Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative; and
•
Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.
We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us. However, we do consider requests made through your password protected account sufficiently verified when the request relates to personal information associated with that specific account.
We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.
15. CALIFORNIA DO-NOT-TRACK DISCLOSURES
Without changing or revoking any of Your privacy protections contained in this privacy policy, it is not feasible at this juncture for Job Diagnosis to 'respond' to a 'do not track' signal as those terms appear in Cal. Bus. & Prof. Code $$ 22575(b)(5).
CONTACT
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy,
please contact our privacy officer at:
Privacy Officer
VHMnetwork LLC
270 Greenwich Ave
Greenwich, CT 06830
Fax: [212-430-6360]
Email:
This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it
JobDiagnosis.com has millions of jobs so use this Privacy Policy for any help.
Use of our Website constitutes acceptance of our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policies.
Copyright © 2005 to 2020 [VHMnetwork LLC] All rights reserved. Design, Develop and Maintained by NextGen TechEdge Solutions Pvt. Ltd.
